To be continued...
Have you been traveling much?
I spent a couple years in the jungle south of the Dragon King Mountains.
Then I arrived at Eastport, where I met your father.
He was debating whether to send his daughters to join you.
So Ginger and I volunteered to help get them here.
Is Ginger in town right now?
Yes. She said she was returning to her prince.
You'll be glad to hear it.
I met your master, too.
Do you mean Master Roxy?
Yes. Of course it wasn't my intention, but my third eye certainly terrified her.
I can't say I'm surprised.
Roxy was the one who originally taught me to be afraid of the soup herd.
So, your trip. You got here awfully fast.
Your little sister was eager to arrive.
Which one?
Young Aisha, of course.
She proposed that we accompany a number of merchant caravans as guards.
So we made excellent time.
But it's been a long while since anyone ordered me around like that.
Sounds like she put you through it.
I'm actually not sure how to respond to that.
Laugh. It's funny.
Man, it really has been forever.
What did we used to talk about?
By the way, what happened to Aeris?
Things got complicated.
She decided to go her own way.
Is that so?
I'm positive that wasn't a personal slight against you, Rudeus.
Yeah, right.
She said we weren't well-matched enough.
That could mean a lot of things.
Doesn't mean she hates you.
Have you considered that you may have misunderstood her intent?
I don't know.
Not really.
What else could she possibly have meant?
Wait for me?
Either way, I went through hell for three years without another word from her.
She didn't save me.
Sylphie did.
What's done is done.
Anyway, how long do you plan to be in town?
I leave tomorrow morning.
That's awfully sudden, isn't it?
Perhaps.
But I would rather not impose upon you.
What? You're not imposing?
Rudeus.
Don't look so despondent.
I'll come back again.
And Eris was never very good with words.
Try not to hold that against her too strongly.
If you meet again in the future,
keep a cool head and talk it out.
If I run into her first,
I'll try to get her side of things for you.
I'd appreciate it.
Thank you.
Oh
So that's how it is
Rui Jared
What was that about do you two know each other a long time ago?
They're both survivors of the Laplace war I bet that's left more than a few lasting grudges
Don't worry Rudeus. I have no intention of fighting him
Although it is odd to see him here of all places
Tell me about it. He says he came here to meet me. Oh
I see I suppose that does fit his character
Well, it's time I got going
Come inside. We'll make breakfast
Well take care you too Rui Jared and good luck. Thanks again for all your help. We really appreciate it
Hey Rui Jared
Thanks for your hard work
You're welcome. Don't demand too much from Rudeus now. All right. I know I'll be good
My daddy! And the woman that's living with him isn't the same lady as last time! How am I supposed to trust him?
These things happen, Norn. That doesn't mean your brother is disloyal or faithless.
Forgive me. Remind me of your name one more time.
Who, me? I'm Sylphiette.
Miss Sylphiette, I leave all three of them in your care.
Oh, of course.
Well then, till next time.
Okay, this is a little belated, but welcome home. Glad you made it safe.
Thank you, and I'm glad to see you looking well too.
Um, anyway, it might take a while to get used to living together again, but we'll figure it out.
Yes, sir. And when did you get married to Sylphie? I had no idea that happened. Right? I bet you were surprised too, huh?
I don't remember Sylphiette too well, actually.
Oh wait, brother! I almost forgot! Dad gave me a box of stuff for you to open as soon as we got here.
Here you go!
So what does Dad have to say?
He included a copy of the letter he sent ahead of you, but this one is asking me to enroll you both in school.
Why? I don't want to go to school! My mom taught me enough!
You won't go?
No! I want to be your maid!
You promised I could!
And look! I still carry this thing you gave me everywhere!
Well, at least take the university's entrance exam, and we'll see how you score.
Huh? Ah!
Okay, that's no problem!
Do you want to sign up for it too, as long as we're at it?
Answer him! Our brother is talking to you, Norn!
I don't want to take it. I'm probably going to fail and I won't get in.
Oh, you don't have to worry about getting in. We have the money. They'll admit anyone, as long as you can pay.
If you have to bribe them, then I don't want to go!
I... no, sorry, I phrased that badly. I didn't mean I'm going to bribe them to let you in, I just meant tuition.
Yeah, watch your mouth, Norn! You shouldn't speak to our big brother like that!
But you heard what he said! He just wants to solve everything with money!
That's only because you've been so bad at school your entire life!
Fine, I'll take the stupid test!
Hey, where are you going? We're not done talking yet!
Shut up!
I just can't abide silky children. Don't you agree, big brother?
Listen to me.
Yes?
I don't want to hear you talk down to your sister again.
Why do you think it's okay to treat her that way?
I don't know. It's just like she doesn't even try.
I understand that it may look that way to you, but she's doing her best. Give her a break.
Well, I'll stop if you want me to. I promise.
Aisha says she wants to be our maid instead of going to school. What do you think?
It's true that we've been neglecting the house a bit lately, so if Aisha wants to help out, I would be happy to have her.
I don't know. She's a kid. We have to be the adults here.
Isn't it our whole job to, like, send her to school, broaden her horizons, all that kind of stuff?
I do see what you're getting at, but I think you're underestimating her a little bit.
Aisha's a smart girl, and she'll do well for herself, whether she goes to school or not.
Yeah.
In which case, I would let her choose. Why overthink letting her follow her passion?
I'm more worried about Norn, to be frank. She obviously misses your dad in Ruizyard. She seems very anxious. So we need to take extra good care of her.
Yeah. Agreed.
I love that I can rely on Sylphie. She's almost like Fitz in that way. Or exactly like Fitz in that way.
Was that bossy? Sorry if I sounded full of myself.
Not at all. Thank you. You made perfect sense. I clearly don't know anything about little girls.
So I'm gonna need your advice pretty often.
Of course. That's what being married is all about. I love you.
I know.
Ta-da!
Aisha, that's a perfect score.
Now I don't have to go to school, right? You said your decision depends on my exam score, remember?
I sure did. Okay, go and work out your duties with Sylphie.
Hooray!
Didn't anticipate hiring a maid, much less a sister-shaped one.
As for Norn, her score left something to be desired.
She didn't do terribly, though. A little below average for her age group, but not bad.
So tell me, you know what you want to study?
I don't know all the options off the top of my head, but there are some fun intro classes.
You could try a bunch of different things and pick later. Like, what if...
Okay, then. I'll try living in the dorm.
Not what I expected, but...
Don't let her! Dad told us we had to come here and live with our big brother!
Just shooting her down would be easy. But she did work up the courage to ask directly.
Plus, she fights with Aisha and she can't stand me, so...
Maybe we should give her a little space.
If you're sure, then yeah. I think we can arrange that.
That's not fair! Norn didn't even get a good score in her exam!
Why does she get her way?
I worked hard and I got everything right, so why does she get special treatment?
Relax, Aisha. I'm not humoring her or anything.
The dorms could be a great environment for her. I won't keep her here if she's miserable.
Are you being nicer to her because... because my mom was just a concubine?
A concu... who told you that, Aisha?
My mom told me, and Norn's grandma did too.
Do you like Norn better than me because we're only half-related?
I want to be your sister too!
Aisha, hey! I don't consider Lilia a concubine.
And you're just as much my little sister as Norn is.
But you're different people with different needs.
I only want what's best for both of you.
Okay, fine.
Norn, just for my own peace of mind, I want to go over a few things before you start classes.
The dorms have their own rules, so learn them and follow them.
Study hard and be willing to ask questions.
And treat your friends right.
If you can't commit to that, you'll have to commute from home.
Okay.
Next up, if you ever have any trouble at school, you can always come talk to me or Sylphie.
And, uh, make sure you brush your teeth every morning and before you go to bed.
Okay.
Make sure to bathe regularly.
Do all your homework on time.
Okay.
And try to keep yourself healthy.
Lastly, come visit us.
I want to see you back every ten days or so.
Okay, but why?
Because I worry.
Whatever you say.
Hey, Norn.
I'm so excited for our next class.
I wonder which teacher we're gonna get.
Norn's been at school for a month already.
But I don't think she's made any friends yet and that's starting to worry me.
You seem down lately, boss, you know that?
Do I look down?
Yeah, like the downest.
So, we got you a little present to cheer you up, Meow.
It took us a whole month to get it ready for you.
Sounds like you went all out.
Whoa there!
No peeking till you get home, Meow.
Open it in secret, or no one will catch you.
Okay, this was fine and now I'm scared.
But hey, thank you anyway.
Yeah, don't mention it.
Yeah, we'll do anything for you, boss.
Whatever it is feels soft.
Better not be mice.
May I ask what you're up to?
Oh, nothing much.
Trying to guess what's in this bag without opening it.
Could you accompany me to the student council office?
Oh, yeah, okay.
Right behind you.
Lovely to see you, highness.
Is there something I can help you with?
Yes, perhaps you can.
Some new students in the girls dormitory have been a bit on edge lately.
Oh?
Upon investigation, most of the distress is among small-breasted girls with pretty faces.
Don't tell me Norn got caught up in something bad.
I'll help in any way I can.
Whatever you need.
Today, I'll help in any way I can.
Today, I was able to question one victim directly.
Linia and Persina, it appears.
Demanded the poor girl remove her underwear on the spot for them.
Did they know?
No.
Nice.
with an increasingly full pack
that looks very much like that one.
So if you'll pardon the indelicacy.
I got this bag this morning from Linnea and Priscilla,
but they told me not to look at it,
and I haven't done that yet!
But you're absolutely right that it must be full of you-know-what,
because I certainly wouldn't put a pass
to the fullest stunt like this!
Is that so?
I ask merely as a formality,
but tell me, were they acting on your orders?
No, Highness! They were not.
You claim you had nothing to do with this?
Of course I didn't!
I just got married to the love of my life,
and I certainly wouldn't send them into the dorms
with my little sister living there!
Very well. I'll believe you.
Sincerely appreciated.
Oh, thank goodness.
I thought for a moment that I hadn't been able to satisfy you.
No, no. This incident struck me as odd as well.
After all, why would Rudeus need to indulge in such depravity,
given the time you spend at home?
Sylphie, are you giving the princess reports about-
No! I would never share that with anybody!
My, just trying to get a rise out of you.
But I'm delighted to hear you've been enjoying wedded bliss.
Now, with that out of the way...
Uh, yeah.
I'll go and talk to them.
I think I still know where they are.
Meanwhile, can I entreat you to return these to the victim, Sinus?
Yes, certainly.
Thanks for coming to find me.
And sorry again about all this.
It can't be easy leading him back.
Not... really.
Norn!
Where are you headed?
Afternoon classes are starting soon.
We haven't met.
I serve as the leader of the student council here.
Please call me Ariel.
Um, hello. My name is Norn Greyrat.
Oh.
Pleased to meet you, Norn.
What's the trouble?
Oh, I am...
I'm supposed to go to practice room three, but I don't know.
We can help with that.
Oh, Luke.
Will you show her the way?
Of course.
Shall we then?
Seriously?
What were you thinking?
I got in trouble with the princess for that.
Oh, sorry, Meow.
We didn't mean any harm.
Please don't be mad at us.
I told you it wouldn't work in Meow Look.
Nuh-uh. It was your idea.
You said the boss would love it for sure.
What are Meow looking at, kid?
Make like an egg and scramble.
Hmm?
Oh, no.
First year doesn't know her place.
No need to.
We'll show her who's top dog around here.
Just so you're both aware.
That was my little sister.
Oh, one second thought.
I guess we can let this one slide.
She looks like a charming young lady.
I don't want to hear a word about either of you bothering her.
Wouldn't dream of it.
We're gonna be so good to her.
I'd love to have a real conversation with her.
Oh, well.
I guess we'll just have to take it slow for a while.
We're not back to her relaunch.
We'll just have to take it slow for a while.
You
La-ya-la-ya-la